<PNJ>
    <dialogue1.0 condition="Secrétaire/Passe-portes:NON">
		<phrases1 name="Secretary">Welcome to FactoryTec factory. Please excuse us, we have not been notified of your arrival. \n\nWhat is the reason for your visit?  Do you come in relation to the job offer? </phrases1>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>How do I get out of here?</reaction>
			<goto>2</goto>
		</reponse1>
		<reponse2>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto>0</goto>
		</reponse2>
	</dialogue1.0>
	<dialogue1.1>
		<phrases1 name="Secretary">I still haven't heard from your door passes yet. Can I help you in any other way? </phrases1>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>Ask to see the person in charge</reaction>
			<goto>4</goto>
		</reponse1>
		<reponse2>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto>0</goto>
		</reponse2>
		<reponse3 condition="Secrétaire/Postuler:NON">
			<reaction>Apply: Protector</reaction>
			<goto action="Avancement/Secrétaire/Postuler:OUI">6</goto>
		</reponse3>
	</dialogue1.1>
	<dialogue2.0>
		<phrases1 name="Secretary">Nothing could be easier, you just have to take the opposite way than the one you took to get here.  \nYour door-passes allow you not to be attacked by the mechanical guards or SS.</phrases1>
		<phrases2 name="Leopold">*%Avancement/NomLeopold% sighs* \nExcept we don't have door passes!  \n\n*He then realizes that he spoke aloud*</phrases2>
		<phrases3 name="Secretary">You lost your door-passes! This is a disaster!  \n\nNormally, I don't even have the right to accept you inside if you don't have one!   \nBut I can't force you to go out anyway! Without your door passes, the guards will do their best to kill you! </phrases3>
		<phrases4 name="Secretary">Maybe you could send a letter to the administration to get a receipt. \nFor my part, I can tolerate you going back to the factory, but your access will be very limited. </phrases4>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>Accept</reaction>
			<goto action="Avancement/Secrétaire/Passe-portes:EnCours">3</goto>
		</reponse1>
		<reponse2>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto>0</goto>
		</reponse2>
	</dialogue2.0>
	<dialogue3.0>
		<phrases1 name="Secretary">*The secretary picks up a post tube and documents * \nWell, here's what you need to write your request. Come back to me once you've filled it out.</phrases1>
		<phrases2 name="Adeline">It's very kind of you to help us, without you I don't know what we would have done. \n*Then, She puts the document in the postal tube and gives the tube to the secretary.*</phrases2>
		<phrases3 name="Secretary">There you go, it's posted! \nWe should have a comeback in a few weeks... \n\nIn the meantime, I advise you to apply for one of our job offers so that you can keep busy and earn some money.</phrases3>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>Ask to see the person in charge.</reaction>
			<goto>4</goto>
		</reponse1>
		<reponse2>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto>0</goto>
		</reponse2>
		<reponse3 condition="Secrétaire/Postuler:NON">
			<reaction>Information: job offers</reaction>
			<goto>5</goto>
		</reponse3>
	</dialogue3.0>
	<dialogue4.0>
		<phrases1 name="Adeline">We demand to see the person in charge of these places.</phrases1>
		<phrases2 name="Secretary">Unfortunately, Mr. J, we haven't received anyone for about a year. The only way to meet him is with the caste leaders' agreement. I'll be happy to call them once you've presented me with your door passes.</phrases2>
		<phrases3 name="Adeline">All right, bring them in immediately. We don't have our door passes, but we should have them quickly.</phrases3>
		<phrases4 name="Secretary">No door passes, no caste leaders! I'm sorry. Sorry.</phrases4>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto>0</goto>
		</reponse1>
		<reponse2 condition="Secrétaire/Postuler:NON">
			<reaction>Information: job offers</reaction>
			<goto>5</goto>
		</reponse2>
	</dialogue4.0>
	<dialogue5.0>
		<phrases1 name="Secretary">Mr. J.'s servants are divided into four castes: The Chasseurs take care of tasks related to the outside of the factory. These include hunting, defending FactoryTec, arresting deserters and delivering parcels.</phrases1>
		<phrases2 name="Secretary">Protectors are essentially concerned with internal protection and receive adequate equipment.</phrases2>
		<phrases3 name="Secretary">Citizens carry out less risky tasks and have the inalienable right to vote for the director or to stand as a candidate for election as a director.</phrases3>
		<phrases4 name="Secretary">Finally, Gears are responsible for the repair and maintenance of the machines while being the only ones authorized to sell, buy or make exchanges.</phrases4>
		<phrases5 name="Secretary">We have protective seats available if you are interested.</phrases5>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>Apply: Protector</reaction>
			<goto action="Avancement/Secrétaire/Postuler:OUI">6</goto>
		</reponse1>
		<reponse2>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto>0</goto>
		</reponse2>
	</dialogue5.0>
	<dialogue6.0>
		<phrases1 name="Secretary">Go to Stan, behind you, after the infirmary, he will tell you how to proceed.</phrases1>
		<reponse1>
			<reaction>Leave</reaction>
			<goto action="Avancement/Stan/Postuler:OUI">0</goto>
		</reponse1>
	</dialogue6.0>
 </PNJ>
